Amanda Steele Show. It is time for Things I Learned This Week. Did you know that the white Jesus that
everybody be praying to is actually Cesar Borgia, an Italian cardinal and Condottiero, an illegitimate
son of Pope Alexander V. And in Africa, you know, the church has definitely done its harm, but it
was Alexander, the actual pope, who gave his approval for this person's face to be used as
the face of Christ. The pope said, yeah, my son who I had with this jump off. Yeah, that's that's Jesus
now. Also, did you know that flushing the toilet with the lid up spreads feces and urine through the
air? Oh, yeah. My wife told me that before. They say that this can also be attributed to making your
acne worse. For those who have acne, that is a way to maybe curb that. The last thing. So May 5th is
Cinco de Mayo, Cinco de Mayo. You notice how we didn't pay no attention to that on this show because
we know that it's BS. May 5th is also Murdered and Missing Indigenous People Awareness Day, MMIP. And
you know, in Canada, there is just such a rash of killings of indigenous people, and they're constantly
fighting for the law and the legislation to pay attention and to, you know, really actually center
their voices. So, you know, it's some bullshit when you got to make a whole day because they're really
not paying attention to you.